(Yamanaka) Sanada just wasn't for me.NOTE Sanada.
♬～
(Kakizaki) Let's continue!
(Sanada) I want to see more scenery with everyone.
♬～
Please enter Eternal Boys again NOTE Eternal Boys
I'll try my best to become an idol
thank you!
Our debut song title is "Eternal"
(Imagawa) Here we come! If the debut song is decided
That's what I should do next.
(Fukuko) I asked Ren, my breadwinner, to appear.
I'm going to shoot the music video for "Eternal"
Huh? (Asai) Oh
(Ren) Well, let's have a comedy competition, shall we?
Yes, if you can make me laugh
MV You can come out and do it.
You're so careless... Are you serious?
I'll do it, but is it okay?
We're pretty funny though
Brief Kenpo!
Briefs!
Huh? That's it?
(Imagawa) You're so cocky.
I'm a former popular child actor and your senior.
Hey, I don't know, what are you in?
Is it a commercial?
Don't you know what "mellow" means?
what? Oh, don't you kids know that?
Huh? I don't know either, huh?
I haven't heard of it either (Ishida).
(Imagawa) Huh? I'm sure you've seen it before
Mellow, refreshing, ladylike
Hehe ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
He's not a popular child actor at all.
Noisy! Hahahahaha
You laughed
(Koba) Ima-chan...
(Sato) Oh! Hahahaha
(Koba) It's been a long time, Ima-chan.
(Sato) It's been 15 years since the coming-of-age ceremony?
(Salesperson) Thank you for waiting.
please
Well, let's meet for the first time in 15 years... (Everyone) Good luck!
Do you two meet often?
The younger children are the same age and often play together as a family.
It's been a while since today, but yeah yeah
Recently, I was transferred to a different department and my work is very hard.
Hehe, what have you been up to lately?
Ah... me?
I'm an idol
Huh? Idol? Amazing
Ima-chan is really cool.
Well, idols also have a lot of trouble behind the scenes.
(Sato) What... what's so amazing?
I had to learn the moves quickly.
Swing? (Imagawa) Dance
I could dance!
Camio, do you know that I got married? Camio?
Look, the guy who became a police officer!
Hey, he's finally home again. How's he doing now?
I? I'm not
Because he's everyone's idol
(Koba) Kakke (Sato) Hahahaha
I wanted to chase my dreams too, I thought I could have a child.
You are no longer the main character in your life.
Really, Sato-chan and Koji are elementary school students?
That's right, I went to look at school bags just last week.
Yes, yes, yes, in the past...
Being a girl, I dream of being a princess...
Please go to the toilet for a moment.
I have to buy it for you, Dad, but I understand.
He says he really wants it...
(Imagawa) <<What are you doing? Me≫
≪Is this okay? ≫
⚟♬『Eternal』
⚟♬～
Doesn't it come out (Asai)?
I don't think so (Kakizaki), but are you coming alone?
No, I'm worried that my mother will be with me.
Ren, what were you doing? I was worried (Ren) Not really...
It's not "special", it's already been 30 minutes.
I mean, what happened to your mother?
I don't know, it's Rimu's place anyway NOTE Rimu
Ren, you're late and you don't have that attitude.
Apologize to everyone
Who is Rimu? I'm Ren's younger brother.
The most popular child actor now
It's amazing how all the siblings are popular child actors.
(Asai) My younger brother is already selling better now.
Child actors have short lives, sorry!
You can't survive in this world if you do that.
Okay, I'm quitting now, so what's the point?
Don't cry on set, you're not a kid anymore.
(Ren) Don't run away from the toilet.
Ima-chan...
(knock)
Hey
We can't shoot without you.
(Ren) You can do it without me.
I'm quitting the entertainment industry
why?
(Ren) I'm not a child anymore.
Why can't the old man continue?
It's not selling, so why don't you quit?
If it doesn't sell, I'll keep doing what I love
Can't you?
(Ren) You're miserable even though you're not needed.
miserable?
(Ren) What about you?
I'm saying no one likes me!
That's right
But what if I give up on this dream now?
I think you'll stop liking me too.
"No one thinks about me..." I know that for real.
Well, at least...at least for me.
I want to love myself
So it's okay to be miserable
me for me...
(Imagawa) I want to chase my dreams
♬～
(sound of door opening)
Uncool
♬～
That's uncool
(cry)
(Imagawa) Sanayan...
Imagawa-san is cool
Absolutely... absolutely cool
(cry)
Adults cry too
♬～
I'm sorry
You can also come out and do the MV.
What kind of change in state of mind?
Mellow, refreshing, ladylike
Haha (Imagawa) You, don't make fun of your seniors.
I'll take a picture right away, man...
Okay, let's do it!
(Kakizaki) Yes.
♬～
I don't feel a soul. (Staff) A soul?
(Souta) Nice to meet you, I'm Souta from GentlemenNOTE That's right.
Did you see it?